The jury gets it.
And you do say in the video that as part of trying to have sex with this woman,
you took her furniture shopping, correct?
We actually did look for furniture, yes.
So that was true. You actually took this woman and...
I think so. It's been a long time ago.
How long is that? A long time ago.
But I think so. I do think so.
Is that the only occasion when you took a woman shopping?
I think so.
And you say, and again this has become very famous,
in this video, I just start kissing them.
It's like a magnet. Just kiss. I don't even wait.
And when you're a star, they let you do it.
You can do anything. Grab them by the pussy.
You can do anything. That's what you said, correct?
Well, historically, that's true with stars.
It's true with stars that they can grab women by the pussy?
Well, if you look over the last million years,
I guess that's been largely true.
Not always, but largely true.
Unfortunately or fortunately.
And you consider yourself to be a star?
I think you can say that, yeah.